flashvd.com 2019-05-09

# Flash Downloader - Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy: April 29, 2019

This page lists the types of information that we collect from our users and shows what exactly we use that information for. We want to make sure you are aware of it so that you always see the whole picture of your interaction with us. Please read this Privacy Policy in full as by installing our add - on or visiting our website you express your acceptance of the practices we list here. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, don’t hesitate to contact our Support service. 

### What type of information does Flash Video Downloader collect?

Flash Video Downloader doesn't store any user data on its own servers. We utilize the industry standard third party Google Analytics service to collect certain information about our visitors to better understand their experience. These information include the users' time spent on our site, session length and frequency, return rate, technical information such as browser type, version, screen resolution and more. We don't collect any device identifier or personal information, IP addresses are anonymized before transmitted. 

###  What does Flash Video Downloader do with the information collected? 

We look at the aggregated usage statistics to better understand where Flash Video Downloader needs improving, monitor overall speed issues, error rates. We look at what devices, browsers and resolutions to support. We consider language and other locale information to determine what possible localizations would be most useful to our users. 

### Usage

Data may be used for any purpose.

### Duration

Data may be kept indefinitely.

### How do I opt out?

You can opt [out of the Google Analytics service](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). Other than that you can always opt out by [uninstalling](https://support.google.com/chrome_webstore/answer/2664769?hl=en) our software. 

### Commerce

Your personal identifiable data is never bartered or sold for commercial gain. 

### Advertising

Your personal data is never given to advertisers.

### Law Enforcement

Data is given to law enforcement only when legal process is followed. 

### Contact

If you have questions about this privacy policy, please contact support(at)flashvd.com.
